game-trek.net 2016-04-01

# Privacy Policy

#### PRIVACY POLICY

Last updated February 2014

Game-trek is a one stop shop for gamers from all around the world! Giving you the opportunity to play for free!

Personal Information: Game-Trek, owned and distributed by Capellov LTD, collects personal information when you make your information known, such as by registering, authenticating, making purchases, or interacting with Game-Trek. We may collect certain information about your web usage habits and websites you have visited, which may be shared with third parties and used for advertising

How We Use Your Information: Your information is used to operate and improve our services, fulfill your requests and communicate with you, conduct research, and personalize the content and advertisements provided to you.

Information Sharing: We may share your personal information in limited circumstances, including when we have your consent to do so or when sharing is necessary to protect Us or comply with the law. Our agents and contractors may have access to your information, but only to perform services for Capellov LTD. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties.

Internet Advertising: Our ability to provide free content and services depends on advertising. Some of our ads are displayed based on the page visited, but many of our ads are targeted to you based on your interests and other information we have about you. Game-Trek permits the use of advertising by third party advertisers. Some advertising partners may use cookies or similar technologies to better measure campaign effectiveness, target future campaigns and deliver a more targeted experience to users.

By using this site, you signify your agreement to the Capellov LTDâ€™s Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site.

Capellov LTD may change its privacy policy from time to time

Please contact us with any question you might have at: [alex@game-trek.net](mailto:alex@game-trek.com)
